<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contributing on Chapar</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/contributing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contributing on Chapar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 15:13:21 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/docs/contributing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/contributing/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 15:13:21 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/contributing/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Our Pledge linkWe as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, caste, color, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.&#xA;We pledge to act and interact in ways that contribute to an open, welcoming, diverse, inclusive, and healthy community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Financial Contributions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/contributing/financial-contributions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 15:13:21 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/contributing/financial-contributions/</guid>
      <description>Chapar is an open-source project that relies on the support of the community to continue development. If you find Chapar useful and would like to help support the project, you can make a financial contribution. Financial contributions help cover the costs of hosting, development, and maintenance of the project.&#xA;How to contribute financially linkRegardless of the amount, your financial contribution is greatly appreciated and helps ensure the continued development of Chapar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Contribute</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/contributing/how-to-contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 15:13:21 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/contributing/how-to-contribute/</guid>
      <description>Contribute to code linkContributing to the codebase is a great way to help improve the project. Here’s how you can get started:&#xA;Create a Pull Request link Fork the repository: Click the &amp;ldquo;Fork&amp;rdquo; button in the top right corner of the repository page to create your own copy of the repo. Clone the repository: Clone your forked repository to your local machine using git clone . Create a new branch: Create a new branch for your changes with a descriptive name, such as feature/add-new-feature or fix/bug-description.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
